ADAM RICE WER DEVELOPER

- adamcoltonrice@gmail.com
- **** 812-483-0497
- **♀** Indiana
- **y** easyLamp

in linkedin.com/in/adam-rice-a9b62829

adam-rice

For many years I have had an interest in web development and recently decided to act on this passion. In 2016 I began studying Front-End Web Development full-time at the Turing School of Software & Design. Previously, I have held roles in marketing, sales and customer service after obtaining a MBA from Ball State University. I am willing to relocate.

Skills

WEB DEVELOPMENT

JavaScript

jQuery

HTML/CSS

SASS

React

Ember

Test-driven

Development

Responsive Design

Education

Ball State University
Master's Degree Business Administration

Ball State University
Bachelor's Degree General Studies

Experience

Turing School of Software & Design Front-End Web Development Student

Denver, Colorado Aug 2016 to Current

An intensive 7 month software development training program covering JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Node.js, SASS, AJAX, React, Ember, Electron, ARIA, object-oriented programming, responsive design, test-driven development, web application deployment and client-side development.

myCOI Client Services Representative

Carmel, Indiana Jun 2015 to Jul 2016

Provided assistance to insurance agents, tenants, subcontractors and myCOI clients answering questions regarding the use of the myCOI software as well as insurance inquiries. Volunteered to update the incoming call-queue software for our client services team.

NextGear Capital Field Marketing Specialist

Carmel, Indiana Jun 2014 to Apr 2015

Coordinated nationwide in-auction marketing materials with our field sales executives and auction partners. Collaborated with Business Development department to create marketing campaigns which increased brand awareness & strengthened the relationship with our auction partners. Monitored and approved promotional campaign requests made by field executives based on historical data, adjusting campaigns when necessary.

Customer Service Advisor

Nov 2013 to Jun 2014

Monitored 35 customer service representatives and provided assistance with complicated issues and aggressive customers. Interviewed applicants for the Customer Service Representative position. Volunteered to generate monthly reports using Excel that alerted customers of upcoming payment dates.

Customer Service Representative

Feb 2013 to Nov 2013

Assisted customers regarding financing, auditing & payment issues. Trained new customer service representatives.

Awards

Dealer Services Employee of the Month

lun 2013

Awarded Dealer Services Employee of the Month by the Director of Dealer Services at NextGear Capital.